# **Andrew Bennett**

## Abennett0322@gmail.com

20303 Stone Oak Parkway (210) 878 5297 www.andrew-bennett.me

# **OBJECTIVES**

Experienced in programming languages, software development, data structures, application programming, and organizing hackathons; I am pursuing a career in Software/Mobile App Development at a company with a culture that is both innovative and open to new ideas.

#### **EDUCATION**

University of Texas at San Antonio

December 2017 Computer Science BA, Business Administration minor

- Delta Sigma Pi (Professional Business Fraternity)
- Association for Computing Machinery
- RowdyHacks (2016 & 2017)

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### Booz Allen Hamilton

Software Engineer Intern Oct 2016 - Current

- Convert existing mobile VR project into an HTML5 web app.
- Work with engineers to develop VR environments using Unity3D's game engine.
- Research new technologies, such as WebGL and Three.js, to meet client needs.
- Occasionally build and set up VR Kits for demos.
- Provide IT support and hardware facilitation for the Interactive Multimedia and Gaming Team.
- Assisted in moving team and equipment to a new office building.

## TopGolf San Antonio |

**Bayhost** Aug 2015 - Oct 2016

 Displayed exceptional knowledge of and enthusiasm for our amazing culinary offerings, while delivering TopGolf hospitality at its best.

#### Starplex Boerne Luxury 11 |

Assistant Manager Jan 2013 - May 2015

• Assisted the GM with daily operations.

### Skills

- Java
- Javascript
- C
- C#
- Sed/Awk/Perl
- SQL
- HTML/CSS
- WebGL
- PHP
- WordPress
- Visual Studio
- Unity3D
- Amazon Alexa
- Marketing Chair of Delta Sigma Pi Fall 2014
- Organizer for RowdyHacks 2017 hackathon

# Other Internships

Divvee; Quinten Burke May 2016 – Aug 2016